<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel>
 <title>Northern Ireland Interfaith Forum aggregator</title>
 <link>http://127.0.0.1/niif//niif/aggregator</link>
 <description>Northern Ireland Interfaith Forum - aggregated feeds</description>
 <language>en</language>
<item>
 <title>Worldwide Religion News: &quot;Prosecutors requalify charges against sect leader Grabovoi&quot;</title>
 <link>http://wwrn.org/article.php?idd=21822</link>
 <description>&lt;br&gt;(&quot;Itar-Tass,&quot; June 13, 2006)
&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Moscow, Russia  - Prosecutors have requalified charges against sect leader Grigory Grabovoi from fraud to grand fraud, the defendant’s lawyer Anatoly Gromov told.
&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
 <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2006 19:57:56 +0100</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
 <title>Worldwide Religion News: &quot;Southern Baptists look to boost membership&quot;</title>
 <link>http://wwrn.org/article.php?idd=21823</link>
 <description>&lt;br&gt;by Tim Whitmire (AP, June 12, 2006)
&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Greensboro, USA - There are more than 16.2 million Southern Baptists worshipping in the U.S., but as leaders of America&#039;s largest Protestant denomination gather this week, they are worried about how to attract new members.
&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
 <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2006 19:57:56 +0100</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
 <title>Worldwide Religion News: &quot;Bishops urge Mexicans to vote in July&quot;</title>
 <link>http://wwrn.org/article.php?idd=21824</link>
 <description>&lt;br&gt;(AP, June 13, 2006)
&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mexico City, Mexico - Mexico&#039;s Roman Catholic Church on Monday urged voters to participate in the July 2 presidential election and asked the candidates to run clean campaigns.
&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
 <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2006 19:57:56 +0100</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
 <title>Worldwide Religion News: &quot;Church to address fallout over gay bishop&quot;</title>
 <link>http://wwrn.org/article.php?idd=21825</link>
 <description>&lt;br&gt;by Rachel Zoll (AP, June 12, 2006)
&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;New York, USA - Three years after confirming its first openly gay bishop, the U.S. Episcopal Church must decide whether to appease irate Anglicans by promising not to do it again — at least for now.
&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
 <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2006 19:57:56 +0100</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
 <title>Worldwide Religion News: &quot;Rajasthan govt re-sends anti-conversion bill&quot;</title>
 <link>http://wwrn.org/article.php?idd=21826</link>
 <description>&lt;br&gt;(&quot;NDTV,&quot; June 13, 2006)
&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jaipur, India - The Vasundhara Raje government has re-sent the controversial Freedom of Religion bill to the Rajasthan Governor Pratibha Patil.
&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
 <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2006 19:57:56 +0100</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
 <title>Worldwide Religion News: &quot;Rabbi Amar Urges China to Officially Recognize Judaism&quot;</title>
 <link>http://wwrn.org/article.php?idd=21827</link>
 <description>&lt;br&gt;(&quot;IsraelNN,&quot; June 13, 2006)
&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Shanghai, China - Chief Rabbi of the State of Israel and Rishon LeZion, Rabbi Shlomo Amar, urged China to extend official state recognition to Judaism. As of now, the Chinese state officially recognizes Protestantism, Catholicism, Buddhism, Taoism and Islam.
&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
 <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2006 19:57:56 +0100</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
 <title>Worldwide Religion News: &quot;Buddhism With a New Mind-Set&quot;</title>
 <link>http://wwrn.org/article.php?idd=21828</link>
 <description>&lt;br&gt;by Michael Luo (&quot;NY Times,&quot; June 13, 2006)
&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;New York, USA - Western spiritual seekers who have focused on meditation have fueled a remarkable growth in Buddhist practice in the United States. So what to do if you are part of an ancient Buddhist tradition that is huge in Asia but has failed to catch on in the United States, in part because it has no real place for meditation?
&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
 <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2006 19:57:56 +0100</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
 <title>Worldwide Religion News: &quot;Judge rejects atheist&#039;s lawsuit&quot;</title>
 <link>http://wwrn.org/article.php?idd=21829</link>
 <description>&lt;br&gt;by Steve Lawrence (AP, June 13, 2006)
&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sacramento, USA - A federal judge on Monday rejected a lawsuit from an atheist who said having the phrase &quot;In God We Trust&quot; on U.S. coins and dollar bills violated his First Amendment rights.
&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
 <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2006 19:57:56 +0100</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
 <title>Worldwide Religion News: &quot;Religious Leaders Urge U.S. to Ban Torture&quot;</title>
 <link>http://wwrn.org/article.php?idd=21830</link>
 <description>&lt;br&gt;by Alan Cooperman (&quot;Washington Post,&quot; June 13, 2006)
&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Washington, USA - Twenty-seven religious leaders, including megachurch pastor Rick Warren, Nobel laureate Elie Wiesel and Cardinal Theodore E. McCarrick of Washington, have signed a statement urging the United States to &quot;abolish torture now -- without exceptions.&quot;
&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
 <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2006 19:57:56 +0100</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
 <title>Worldwide Religion News: &quot;A most unlikely genre: Amish crime thrillers&quot;</title>
 <link>http://wwrn.org/article.php?idd=21831</link>
 <description>&lt;br&gt;By David Horn (&quot;Christian Science Monitor,&quot; June 13, 2006)
&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Wooster, USA - Paul L. Gaus teaches chemistry at the College of Wooster in Wooster, Ohio, but for the past quarter century he&#039;s also traveled Amish backroads, making friends while collecting stories and anecdotes. Gaus is an Amishlieben, or friend of the Amish, who&#039;s lived side by side with the Plain People of Holmes County, Ohio, long enough to understand and respect their traditions and values.
&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
 <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2006 19:57:56 +0100</pubDate>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
